Shruti Khandekar, Web Developer

San Diego, CA, (858) 926-8476, shrutikhandekar1@gmail.com

LINKS	https://www.linkedin.com/in/shrutikhandekar/, https://shrutikhandekar1.github.io/My-Portfolio/#		
PROFILE	Highly motivated recent graduate with Advanced Certificate in Web and Mobile Application Development (GPA of 3.26), with many years of prior experience as Sr. Quality Assurance Engineer at large companies. Mature and dedicated professional with training in design principles and programming languages, seeking opportunity in Web Application Development and Testing.		
SKILLS	JavaScript	Ajax	
	HTML5/CSS3	CSS3 GitHub	
	ReactJS	MongoDB/SQL	
	Java	Windows 2000/NT/XP, Solaris	
	Express/NodeJS	SPARC, Linux and UNIX	
EDUCATION			
Jul 2018 — May 2020	Advanced Certificate in Web And Mobile Application, San Diego State University San I		n Diego
Jun 1999 — Aug 2002	Bachelor of Engineering, Pune University Instrumentation Engineering Pune, India		Pune, India
PROJECTS			
Jul 2018 — May 2020	Product Inventory		
	Used MERN stack to create a full-stack product Inventory application. Displayed knowledge in CRUD (Create, Update, Delete) operations. Pull in data from the MongoDB server and display inventory in tabulated format on an SPA using ReactJS. Used Express in the back-end. Added routing for the Single Page App using React-router.		
	Corporate website		
	Created a four-page website for a sample corporation using MERN stack. The website included web pages for Home, About Us, Solutions, and Contact Us. Added Grid layouts and used SASS for styling the webpage.		
	Employee Management System		
	Built an Employee Management application that allowed the user to show all employees, add an employee, and delete an employee. Used multi-dimensional data to persist employee data.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Mar 2010 — Jul 2012	Sr Software Quality Assurance Specialist, Oracle Corp Los Angele		Angeles
	Worked on creating frameworks for both client and server-side test automation for Oracle SOA suite. Worked as part of scrum team, for product development for upcoming releases of Oracle SOA product.		
Dec 2003 — Feb 2010	Programmatic Automation Engineer, Sun Microsystems Los Ang		Angeles
	Created manual tests and automated test harness for both web-based and client-server based java application which ran successfully on all windows, Linux and Unix platforms.		